Nepal Church History Project Archives
Yale University Divinity School Library
Nepal Church History Project Records
1896-2007
RG 215
Yale University Divinity School Library
31
70 boxes, 1 oversize box
The Nepal Church History Project began in 1985 as an initiative of local church leaders in Nepal to research and collect materials relevant to the history of Christianity among the Nepali peoples. The objective of the Project is to preserve, maintain and update a comprehensive, organized documentary record of the Nepali Church from its inception, and to make available documents and information as appropriate to researchers, students and other interested users.
Nepal Church History Project
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Gift of the Nepal Church History Project
Custodial History
Previously held at the Center for the Study of Christianity in the Non-Western World, University of Edinburgh
Information about Access
This collection is open to qualified researchers.
History
The Nepal Church History Project was an initiative of local church leaders in Nepal to research and collect materials relevant to the history of Christianity among the Nepali peoples. It began in 1985 and continues under the chairmanship of Dr Rajendra Rongong of Kathmandu. The objective of the Project is to preserve, maintain and update a comprehensive, organized documentary record of the Nepali Church from its inception, and to make available documents and information as appropriate to researchers, students and other interested users.
The roots of the Nepali Church can be traced back to 19th century Scottish and Scandinavian missionaries working among Nepali migrants in North-East India. As in the 1950s Darjeeling was the base from which Nepali evangelists returned to Nepal, in 1998 it was the venue of the Himalayan Congress of Evangelism (HIM-COE) that gathered Nepali Christian leaders dispersed around the world. Nepali Church evangelism is today concerned to spread the Gospel among Nepalis at home and throughout the Nepali diaspora.
In1951 the Kingdom of Nepal opened its frontiers to the external world. Christians, for the first time in two hundred years, were allowed to settle in the country. Church growth was initially slow, and Christians were vulnerable to social and legal persecution. From a few hundred Nepali Christians in the 1950s and 1960s, their number is now in excess of 300,000. This represents one of the fastest rates of church growth in Asia.
The NCHP documentation was originally located in the Centre for the Study of Christianity in the Non-Western World (CSCNWW), Faculty of Divinity, University of Edinburgh, Scotland. It was there that Dr Cindy Perry, Coordinator of NCHP, conducted her pioneer research on the Nepali Church, the preliminary fruits of which have been published in her Biographical History of the Church in Nepal (Kathmandu: Nepal Church History Project, 1990), and Nepalis Around the World (Kathmandu: RC Timothy, Ekta Books Distributors, 1997).
Description of the Papers
The collection includes correspondence, reports, and documents relating to the early history of Nepali Church in North India, its development in Nepal since 1951, and its outreach in the wider diaspora countries. It also includes photographs relating to the same three divisions, teaching materials published in Nepal and India by the Nepali Church and by Christian missions, including Bibles and hymnbooks, and published materials, both Christian and secular, relevant to the Nepali Church. The materials have been organized according to a numerical classification system devised by the Project. This finding aid provides an outline of the files. A searchable database that provides document-level description is available at the repository.
Arrangement
Series I, A - Church in Nepal
Series II, B -Diaspora
Series III, C - Audio Visual Nepali Language or Church Related Media Collection
Series IV, D - Nepali Christian Literature Collection
Series IV, E - Nepali Christian Magazines
Series VI, F - Church Survey
Series VII, G - Photograph Collection
Series VIII, H - Book and Pamphlet Collection
Series IX, I - Nepali Bible and Hymnal/Songbook Collection
Series X - Regarding the NCHP
Series XI - Addendum
Missions -- Nepal
- A - Church in Nepal, Series I
  - A01: Pre-1950s Missions / Christian work among Nepalis
    - A 01 01 01 General, 1931, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - A 01 02 01 American Baptist Church, 1914 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - A 01 03 01 Assemblies of God and Beckdahls and Barnabas Rai, 1906-1986 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - A 01 04 01 Australian Nepalese Mission, 1977-1987, n.d. (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - A 01 05 01 Brethren In Christ, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - A 01 06 01 Ceylon India General Mission/International Christian Fellowship and Ralph Cunningham, 1930-1986 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - A 01 07 01 Church Of England, 1908 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - A 01 08 01 Good Shepherd Agricultural Mission, 1951-1987 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - A 01 09 01 Gorakhpur Nurseries Fellowship, 1969-1986 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - A 01 10 01 Methodist Episcopal Church and Martha Sheldon, 1936-1969 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - A 01 11 01 Nepal Border Fellowship/Nepal Prayer Fellowship - General, 1937-1994 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - A 01 11 02 Nepal Border Fellowship/Nepal Prayer Fellowship - Reports, Minutes, Circulars etc., 1944-1960 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - A 01 11 03 Nepal Border Fellowship/Nepal Prayer Fellowship - Correspondence, 1946-1954 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - A 01 12 01 Nepal Evangelistic Band (See also separate NEB/INF collection), 1978-1991 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - A 01 13 01 Nepaul Mission / J. Innes Wright, 1896-1902 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - A 01 14 01 Raxaul Medical Mission, 1935-1987 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - A 01 15 01 Regions Beyond Missionary Union & Raxaul & Elizabeth Franklin Correspondence, 1896-1987 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - A 01 16 01 Roman Catholic Missions, 1902-1991 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - A 01 17 01 Swedish Baptists / Orebro, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - A 01 18 01 Tibetan Frontier Mission & Steiners, 1930-1987 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - A 01 19 01 UMN & Pioneer Treks, 1949 & 1951-52 (see also UMN Archives), 1940-1987 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - A 01 20 01 WEC (Worldwide Evangelization Crusade) - General, 1936-1994 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - A 01 20 02 WEC (Worldwide Evangelization Crusade) - Field Leaders' Reports / Newsletters, 1949-1971 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - A 01 20 03 WEC (Worldwide Evangelization Crusade) - Hester Withey Prayer Letters, etc., 1952-1978 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - A 01 20 04 WEC (Worldwide Evangelization Crusade) - Beth Allinger Correspondence, Prayer Letters etc., 1949-1998 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - A 01 21 01 World Mission Prayer League - General, 1944-1990 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - A 01 21 02 World Mission Prayer League - Roy & Alma Hagen Letters (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - A 01 22 01 Dr. Katherine Young In India & Dandeldhura, 1958-1996 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - A 01 23 01 ZBMM/BMMF & Kitty Harbord - General, 1928-1987 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - A 01 23 02 ZBMM/BMMF & Kitty Harbord - Letters To Jonathan Lindell From Dr. Kitty Harbord 1942-44, 1942-1980 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - A02: Missions in Nepal (Post revolution, 1950s onwards)
    - A 02 01 01 BMS, 1984-1989 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - A 02 02 01 BMMF / Interserve, 1956-1993 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - A 02 03 01 SIM (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - A 02 04 01 CMS, UK (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - A 02 05 01 Impact Asia, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - A 02 06 01 INF - Church-Related (see also INF Archives), 1977-1994 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - A 02 06 01 INF - Church-Related (see also INF Archives) (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - A 02 07 01 The Leprosy Mission, 1984-1986 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - A 02 08 01 MAF, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - A 02 09 01 Methodist Church, UK, 1984-1991 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - A 02 09 02 Methodist Church, USA, 1954-1962, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - A 02 10 01 Nepal Leprosy Trust (NLT), 1975-2001 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - A 02 11 01 Roman Catholics, 1952-1985 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - A 02 12 01 SDA, Banepa, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - A 02 13 01 TEAM, 1970-1994 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - A 02 14 01 Tear Fund, 1986, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - A 02 15 01 UMN & Church (see also UMN Archives), 1954-1994 (Box 4, Folder 16,17)
    - A 02 16 01 Wycliffe, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - A 02 17 01 Ministries Network, Kathmandu (formerly Himalayan Ministries) (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - A 02 18 01 Church-Mission Relationships (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - A 02 19 01 Nepal Leprosy Fellowship (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - A 02 20 01 Nepal-Mission (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - A03: Christian Organizations in Nepal
    - A 03 01 01 General (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - A 03 01 01 General (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - A 03 02 01 Aglow, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - A 03 03 01 Asian Outreach, 1985-1991 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - A 03 04 01 Bhutan Camps, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - A 03 05 01 Bible Society In Nepal / Nepal Bible Society - General, 1975-1993 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - A 03 05 02 American Bible Society Publications Re Bible Society In Nepal, 1990-1992 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - A 03 06 01 Christian Professional's Fellowship / Believers' Professionals Fellowship, 1990-1994 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - A 03 07 01 David Evangelistic Outreach, 1976-1987 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - A 03 08 01 FOCUS, 19896-1993 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - A 03 09 01 Gideons, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - A 03 10 01 Gospel For Asia, Nepal & Bodhartha Prakashan, 1991-1995 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - A 03 11 01 Gospel Recordings, 1951-1993 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - A 03 12 01 Great Commission, 1987-1991 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - A 03 13 01 HDCS (NCF), 1993 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - A 03 14 01 Hospital Christian Fellowship, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - A 03 15 01 International Bible Society Nepal, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - A 03 16 01 International Needs, 1988-1995 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - A 03 17 01 NBCBS, 1978-2001 (Box 6, Folder 1, 2)
    - A 03 18 01 NCCEF / Bal Sangati, 1983-1996 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - A 03 19 01 NCF Hostel, 1961-1975 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - A 03 20 01 Nepal Campus Crusade For Christ, 1978-1994 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - A 03 21 01 Nepal Christian Nurses Fellowship, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - A 03 22 01 Nepal Evangelistic Teams, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - A 03 23 01 Nepal Every Home Concern, 1983-2000 (Box 7, Folder 1, 2)
    - A 03 24 01 Nepal Gospel Outreach Centre, 1993-2001 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - A 03 25 01 Korean Epilepsy Association (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - A 03 26 01 Nepal Pen Pals, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - A 03 27 01 Nepal Prayer Fellowship, 1982-1994 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - A 03 28 01 Nepal Youth For Christ, 1969-1981 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - A 03 29 01 New Life, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - A 03 30 01 Operation Mobilisation, 1964-2001 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - A 03 31 01 Orphanages - Ghar-Aangan, Kathmandu, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - A 03 31 02 Orphanages - Hallelujah Children's Haven, 1989-1990 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - A 03 31 03 Orphanages - Mendies Haven, 1987-1991 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - A 03 31 04 Orphanages - Nepal Christian Orphanage, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - A 03 31 05 Orphanages - Salvation Children's Home, 1998-2001 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - A 03 31 06 Orphanages - Sahara Children's Home (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - A 03 31 07 Orphanages – New Life Home (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - A 03 32 01 Prison Fellowship, 1991-1994 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - A 03 33 01 Sowers Ministry, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - A 03 34 01 Teachers' Christian Fellowship Of Nepal / Nepal Christian Teacher's Fellowship, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - A 03 35 01 Teach Ministries, 1997-1999 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - A 03 36 01 Witness For Nepal, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - A 03 37 01 Youth With A Mission, 1985-1994 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - A 03 38 01 YWCA, Nepal, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - A 03 39 01 YMCA, Nepal, 1994-1996 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - A 03 40 01 Christian Business Centre, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - A 03 41 01 Christian Cemetery, Kathmandu, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - A 03 42 01 Christian Study And Research Centre, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - A 03 43 01 Christian Women Society, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - A 03 44 01 Follow-up & Counseling Center (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - A 03 45 01 Good News Communications Center (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - A 03 46 01 Handicap Care Home, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - A 03 47 01 Himalayan Outreach Mission (HOM-Nepal) (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - A 03 48 01 Himalayan Relief Service, Nepal, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - A 03 49 01 International Fellowship For The Handicapped, 1992-1997 (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - A 03 50 01 Nazareth Educational Services (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - A 03 51 01 Outreach Nepal Ministries, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 27)
    - A 03 52 01 Peace Rehabilitation Center (Shanti Punarsthapana Griha), 1998 (Box 8, Folder 28)
    - A 03 53 01 Share And Care, 1993-1994 (Box 8, Folder 29)
    - A 03 54 01 Students' Fellowship House (Kathmandu Tyrannus Hall), 1991-1996 (Box 8, Folder 30)
    - A 03 55 01 Scripture Union, Nepal, 1992-1998 (Box 8, Folder 31)
    - A 03 56 01 Disciples for Christ, Nepal, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 32)
    - A 03 57 01 Help the Children, Street Children Ministry, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 33)
    - A 03 58 01 Himalayan Cruisider For Christ, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 34)
    - A 03 59 01 Prabodh Group, 1999-2002 (Box 8, Folder 35)
    - A 03 60 01 Dirgha Memorial Mission (Box 8, Folder 36)
    - A 03 61 01 Nepal Christian Students Fellowship (Box 8, Folder 37)
    - A 03 62 01 MTH Nepal, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 38)
    - A 03 63 01 Shanti Punarstapana Ghreeha, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 39)
    - A 03 64 01 Indreni - Ministry, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 40)
    - A 03 65 01 Forward Looking (Box 8, Folder 41)
    - A 03 66 01 Kids Learning Centre, 1996-1998 (Box 8, Folder 42)
    - A 03 67 01 Solidarity International Academy, Nepal, 2001-2003 (Box 8, Folder 43)
    - A 03 68 01 Missions Commission Of Nepal, 2004 (Box 8, Folder 44)
    - A 03 69 01 Nepal Mission Training Center, ca. 2001 (Box 8, Folder 45)
    - A 03 70 01 United Christian Service Network In Nepal (Box 8, Folder 46)
  - A04: Church Files and Associations of Churches in Nepal
    - A 04 01 01 Church Files - General Historical, 1969-1999 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - A 04 01 02 Church Files - 1950-59, 1950-1959 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - A 04 01 03 Church Files - 1960-69, 1960-1969 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - A 04 01 04 Church Files - 1970-79, 1970-1979 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - A 04 01 04 Church Files - 1970-79, 1970-1979 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - A 04 01 05 Church Files - 1980-89, 1980-1989 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - A 04 01 06 Church Files - 1990-99, 1990-1999 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Agape Fellowship & Southampton UK Connection, 1987, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - A 04 03 01 Assembly Of God & Discipleship Training Centre, Kathmandu, 1986-1993 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - A 04 04 01 Baptists In Nepal, 1993-2003 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - A 04 05 01 Evangelical Christian Alliance Of Nepal / Four-Square, 1990-1996 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - A 04 06 01 Evangelical Christian Fellowship Of Nepal, 1994-1996 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - A 04 07 01 Kathmandu Interchurch Relationships, 1957-1993 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - A 04 08 01 Nepal Christian Fellowship, 1960-1981 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - A 04 08 02 Nepal Christian Fellowship, 1982-1989 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - A 04 08 03 Nepal Christian Fellowship / National Churches Fellowship Nepal, 1990-1999 (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - A 04 08 04 National Churches Fellowship Nepal, 2000- (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - A 04 09 01 Isai Nari Samaj, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - A 04 10 01 Nepal Christian Society, 1996-1999 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - A 04 11 01 Nepal Alliance Of Presbyterian Churches, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - A 04 12 01 Nepal Christian Forum, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - A 04 13 01 Nepal Christian United Fellowship, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - A 04 15 01 Roman Catholic Churches In Nepal, 1991-1997 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - A 04 16 01 Evangelical Friends Church Nepal, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - A 04 17 01 El Shaddai Churches, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - A 05 Individual Churches in Nepal
    - A 05 01 01 General - Miscellaneous, 1959-1994 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - A 05 01 02 General - Anchal Church Outlines, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - A 05 02 01 Amp Pipal, Gorkha, 1959-1987 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - A 05 03 01 Aradhana Mandali, Kathmandu, 1980-1988 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - A 05 04 01 Bagh Bazaar, Pokhara, 1971-1993 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - A 05 05 01 Baglung & Ellen Meincke Notes, 1961-1987 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - A 05 06 01 Barpak, 1978-1996 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - A 05 07 01 Bhaktapur, Pastor Tir Bahadur Dewan & Denis Roche Prayer Letters From 1987, 1986-2004 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - A 05 08 01 Bharatpur (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - A 05 09 01 Biratnagar, 1970 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - A 05 10 01 Birganj, 1987,1993 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - A 05 11 01 Butwal, 1965-2000 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - A 05 12 01 Chepangs, 1984-1993 (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - A 05 13 01 Church Of God, 1988-1992 (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - A 05 14 01 Dhanwar Rais, 1975-1987 (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - A 05 15 01 Dharan, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - A 05 16 01 Ghorahi, Dang, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - A 05 17 01 Gyaneshwar, Kathmandu / Nepali Isai Mandali, 1961-2003 (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - A 05 18 01 Hetauda, Ratmate, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - A 05 19 01 Jhimruk, 1992-1993 (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - A 05 20 01 Jumla, 1989-1994 (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - A 05 21 01 Kathmandu Valley - Miscellaneous Churches, 1983-2000 (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - A 05 22 01 Lamagara, Tamang Churches, 1981-1984 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - A 05 23 01 Nepalganj, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - A 05 24 01 Okhaldhunga, 1966-1987 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - A 05 25 01 Paimey, 1987-1999 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - A 05 26 01 Patan Church, 1962-2000 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - A 05 27 01 Putali Sadak, Kathmandu, 1950-2003 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - A 05 28 01 Ramghat, Pokhara, 1957-2002 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - A 05 29 01 Raxaul, 1964-1987 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - A 05 30 01 Santals, 1957 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - A 05 31 01 Sherpas, 1986-1987 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - A 05 32 01 Surkhet, 1987-1996 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - A 05 33 01 Tansen, 1955-1992 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - A 05 34 01 Tikapur, 1982-1987 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - A 05 35 01 Khimti (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - A 05 36 01 Bhairawa (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - A 05 37 01 Morang District (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - A 05 38 01 Jharlang (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - A 05 39 01 Nawal Parasi (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - A 05 40 01 Baitadi (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - A 05 41 01 Galyang (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - A 05 42 01 Jajarkot (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - A 05 43 01 Pokhara (Box 12, Folder 22)
    - A 05 44 01 Dhading (Box 12, Folder 23)
    - A 05 45 01 Aashish Mandali, Dhankuta (Box 12, Folder 24)
    - A 05 46 01 Mugu (Box 12, Folder 25)
    - A 05 47 01 Anandit Church, Koteshwar, Kathmandu (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - A06: Individual Nepali Christians
    - A 06 01 01 General (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - A 06 02 01 Acharya, Rishi Raj (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - A 06 03 01 Bhatt, David (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - A 06 04 01 Dewan, Tir Bahadur & Ratan Bhaktapur Church (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - A 06 05 01 Eapen, K.S. (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - A 06 07 01 Gurung, Philip & Maili (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - A 06 08 01 Gurung, Priscilla (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - A 06 09 01 Juriboo, Manamit (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - A 06 10 01 Kashinath (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - A 06 11 01 Karthak, Robert (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - A 06 12 01 Khatry, Ramesh (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - A 06 13 01 Khawas, Bir (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - A 06 14 01 Leela, Chandra (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - A 06 15 01 Limbu, Chandra Singh Loksam (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - A 06 16 01 Lokman (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - A 06 17 01 Lucius (Bhim Bahadur Lama) (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - A 06 18 01 Masih, Daud & Soni (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - A 06 19 01 Masih, Prem (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - A 06 20 01 Mathai, Mr. & Mrs. M. (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - A 06 21 01 Mose (Box 13, Folder 20)
    - A 06 22 01 Mukhia, Pastor David & Premi (Box 13, Folder 21)
    - A 06 23 01 Mukhia, Shillingford & Martha (Box 13, Folder 22)
    - A 06 24 01 Paudel, Resham Raj & Sita (Box 13, Folder 23)
    - A 06 25 01 Phipon, Attan Tshering (Box 13, Folder 24)
    - A 06 26 01 Phulmaya (Box 13, Folder 25)
    - A 06 27 01 Pradhan, Daniel & Martha (Box 13, Folder 26)
    - A 06 28 01 Pradhan, Ganga Prasad, & Harkadhoj (Box 13, Folder 27)
    - A 06 29 01 Pradhan, Prem - General (Box 13, Folder 28)
    - A 06 29 02 Pradhan, Prem - Christian Aid Publications / Reports (Box 13, Folder 29)
    - A 06 30 01 Rai, Barnabas (Box 13, Folder 30)
    - A 06 31 01 Rai, Bir Bahadur & Ruth (Box 13, Folder 31)
    - A 06 32 01 Rai, Bishnu (Box 13, Folder 32)
    - A 06 33 01 Rai, Hastaman (Box 13, Folder 33)
    - A 06 34 01 Rai, P. B. (Box 13, Folder 34)
    - A 06 35 01 Rajan, Peter (Box 13, Folder 35)
    - A 06 36 01 Rana, Nararaj Shamsher Jung Bahadur (Box 13, Folder 36)
    - A 06 37 01 Ranglal, Pandit (Box 13, Folder 37)
    - A 06 38 01 Rokaya, Kali Bahadur & Draupadi (Box 13, Folder 38)
    - A 06 39 01 Rongong, Adon & Mannu (Box 13, Folder 39)
    - A 06 40 01 Rongong, Birendra (Box 13, Folder 40)
    - A 06 41 01 Rongong, Rajendra (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - A 06 42 01 Shah, Gyani (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - A 06 43 01 Sherpa, Rebecca (Singh) (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - A 06 44 01 Sherpa, Sambha (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - A 06 45 01 Silal, Gautam (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - A 06 46 01 Simon (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - A 06 47 01 Simon-Peter / Nepal, Ram Sharan (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - A 06 48 01 Singh, Debu & Rita (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - A 06 49 01 Singh, Magdalini & Goman (Magdalene / Chitrawati) (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - A 06 50 01 Singh, Peter Kamaleshwar (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - A 06 51 01 Singh, Ranbir Bekhim (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - A 06 52 01 Sitling, Daniel & Itmanon (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - A 06 53 01 Tamang, Lok Bahadur (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - A 06 54 01 Tamang, Nicanor & Elizabeth (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - A 06 55 01 Tamang, Noah & Hannah (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - A 06 56 01 Thapa, Hari Bahadur (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - A 06 57 01 Thapa, Tirtha (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - A 06 58 01 Thapa, Yacub & Rebecca (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - A 06 59 01 Tiwari, Joshua (Gokal) Prasadh (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - A 06 60 01 Bhandiri, Lok Mani (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - A 06 61 01 Chettri, Chitra B. (Box 14, Folder 21)
    - A 06 62 01 Dhakal, Hom Nath (Box 14, Folder 22)
    - A 06 63 01 DeCruse, Amzad A. W. (Box 14, Folder 23)
    - A 06 64 01 Karthak, Samuel (Box 14, Folder 24)
    - A 06 65 01 Sodemba, Shri Sonhang (Box 14, Folder 25)
    - A 06 66 01 Sharma, Bal Krishna (Box 14, Folder 26)
    - A 06 67 01 Tamang, Kali Bahadur (Box 14, Folder 27)
    - A 06 68 01 Subba, Samuel & Lakmati (Box 14, Folder 28)
    - A 06 69 01 Thapa, Daniel (Box 14, Folder 29)
    - A 06 70 01 Mukhia, Ruth (Box 14, Folder 30)
    - A 06 71 01 Bhandari, Tek Bahadur (Box 14, Folder 31)
    - A 06 72 01 Nepali, Purushotam & Dilly (Box 14, Folder 32)
    - A 06 73 01 Sharma, Damodar (Box 14, Folder 33)
  - A07 Bible Trainings for Nepalis
    - A 07 01 01 ABEN & Consultation On Theological Education In Nepal, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - A 07 02 01 Miscellaneous (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - A 07 03 01 Agape Bible School, Pokhara (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - A 07 04 01 Bible Training Centre For Pastors (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - A 07 05 01 Church Builders' Bible Institute (David Cloud) (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - A 07 06 01 DBCI / NBCI (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - A 07 07 01 Darjeeling Hills Bible School, Mirik (Box 18, Folder 19)
    - A 07 08 01 Discipleship Training Centre, Lalitpur (Box 18, Folder 20)
    - A 07 09 01 Doon Bible College, Dehra Dun (Box 18, Folder 21)
    - A 07 10 01 Great Commission Training Centre, Kathmandu (Box 18, Folder 22)